<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>The Backrooms - new forum threads</title>
		<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/start</link>
		<description>Threads in forums of the site &quot;The Backrooms&quot; - You&#039;ve been here before.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 09:09:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17453191</guid>
				<title>Level 878 - &quot;The Lasting Warmth&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17453191/level-878-the-lasting-warmth</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Wynths</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9594206</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>omg I forgot this was the fragment</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17452152</guid>
				<title>Object C-1 - &quot;Canned Dragon Meat&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17452152/object-c-1-canned-dragon-meat</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>calf-0</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9454668</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Placeholder</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17449945</guid>
				<title>Phenomenon 10 - Hamelin Harmony</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17449945/phenomenon-10-hamelin-harmony</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 15:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Light_Nate</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9514519</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <h1><span>+1</span></h1> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17449293</guid>
				<title>An Bhean ar Árasán 2000</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17449293/an-bhean-ar-arasan-2000</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:18:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>KillerOreo52</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9751782</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It looks amazing btw, I'll probably read later :3</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17449071</guid>
				<title>What She Tried To Teach Me</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17449071/what-she-tried-to-teach-me</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 07:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>scutoid studios</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>8055329</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The poem is a bit short, and it doesn't do much original with the folk tale, playing it pretty straight to the point of summarization. I think the folk tale you picked has a lot of good potential as a Backrooms thing, and if you'd had the time to write your rice paddy level it might have turned out way better. As it stands, it's just got to be developed some more. You can also integrate the Buddhist aspect better, which I can't lie I didn't really cop when I read it. j</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17449019</guid>
				<title>Selenophilia / The Goddess</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17449019/selenophilia-the-goddess</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 06:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Wynths</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9594206</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>7 and a half months ago, <span class="printuser avatarhover"><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/yossipossi" ><img class="small" src="https://www.wikidot.com/avatar.php?userid=2199269&amp;amp;size=small&amp;amp;timestamp=1763391119" alt="Yossipossi" style="background-image:url(https://www.wikidot.com/userkarma.php?u=2199269)" /></a><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/yossipossi" >Yossipossi</a></span> might have, in a butterfly-effect-esque way, changed the course of my life for years to come.</p> <p>they published, entirely as a joke, the <a href="https://scp-wiki.wikidot.com/totally-legit-scp-anthology-2025" target="_blank">April Fool's SCP Anthology</a> &#8212; a collection of 31 parodic prompts that resembled the real anthology's themes. it was a goof, a gaffe &#8212; something that should have, in all respects, been uninterestingly good.</p> <p>that was not the case for me.</p> <p>I wrote the three parts of ACROPHILIA in four days, and it comprises about 12k words, being by far and away the best example I have for what one can do when possessed by the muse. of course, given the fact that I was a <em>brand</em> new author who had coldposted the articles out of nothing but bull-headed stubbornness (hey&#8230; that seems familiar. note that down for later, maybe.), the two tales went ignored, still holding less than +10 each while the SCP is in only slightly better shape, sitting at +25 as of writing.</p> <p>so, what did i learn from the whole &quot;rush production&quot; style of writing, and the obvious damage which it did to the potential reception of those articles?</p> <p>simple &#8212; i did it again.</p> <div class="collapsible-block"> <div class="collapsible-block-folded"><a class="collapsible-block-link" href="javascript:;">+&nbsp;lengthy&nbsp;ramblings,&nbsp;1024&nbsp;words&nbsp;</a></div> <div class="collapsible-block-unfolded" style="display:none"> <div class="collapsible-block-unfolded-link"><a class="collapsible-block-link" href="javascript:;">-&nbsp;Close</a></div> <div class="collapsible-block-content"> <p>i am both incredibly proud of Selenophilia for the monstrous amount of words i was able to put in while still keeping A Degree of quality, and the amount of Things and Ideas I was able to integrate into the whole project (so much so that, if this thing gets popular, i'll probably put out a &quot;director's cut&quot; version where i explain my moment-to-moment writing style and the Things and Ideas that influenced how this thing came out.)</p> <p>there are, of course, a couple of general things which i can talk about now &#8212; the first being, what to any wiki author must be, a sun-bright decision to <em>coldpost</em> this entire thing. while i cannot stress enough how much i do not <em>endorse</em> this sort of reckless and irresponsible behavior, i do feel like, in order to embark on some of my wildest and most <em>clearly</em> ROI-negative pieces, such as this one, coldposting serves as a way to make working on pieces like this &#8212; which i do find fun &#8212; worth it in my mind. i also think it encourages me, whenever time isn't <em>as</em> much a pressure, to give much tighter writing and editing to my pieces, as i don't have the incredibly luxury of having people look over it before i publish on the wiki. of course, this also means that pages don't come out with as even a quality as they could be &#8212; jagged edges will be transparent. regardless, in my <em>personal estimation</em>, this is worth it in order to be able to swallow the pill of, say, writing a 17.2k word piece on a site which is explicitly <span style="text-decoration: underline;">not</span> equipped for such bullshit.</p> <p>another couple things with regard the structure of the piece:<br /> 1) the poem at the end doesn't <span style="text-decoration: underline;">necessarily</span> have to be there, i'm well aware of that. the reason that i spent so much time on it anyways is because i felt like, in a story which primarily occurs in a world that is completely unrecognizable from <em>anything</em> on the site, being able to tie some familiarity to this world while <span style="text-decoration: underline;">also</span> being able to characterize the titular Goddess and lay bare her incredible fucked-up-ed-ness, was something that would play well with the prose narrative. also, it was grandfahered in from&#8230;</p> <p>2) this thing was <em>not</em> intended to be a folklorecon piece. originally, it was going to be a standalone SCP written to fit more exactly onto the prompt given by the anthology. then, after a coauthored piece for 9kcon fell through due to my coauthor's mental health issues, i tried to hammer the thing into 9kcon worthy shape in about 5 days. it didn't work.</p> <p>then, during the voting period for 9kcon, i saw the announcement that folklorecon was going to happen, and the gears turned in my mind. as stated above, i am an avid fan of coldposting and regularly practice such nonsense myself. realizing that, if i was ever going to participate in the backrooms wiki, i <em>had</em> to have that option at my disposal, i knew that repurposing the 9kcon draft into a folklorecon draft would be the easiest way to ensure that i had something presentable in the timeframe allotted. so, i deleted the SCP portion and carried over the poem to a new backrooms sandbox. &quot;it shouldn't take that long &#8212; how much content can there be here? i want FOREFRONT interludes to be under 10k, i'll just make sure it stays there&quot;</p> <p>that sentiment was <span style="text-decoration: underline;">foolish.</span> if there is something that i am an even stronger advocate for than the right to coldpost, it would be the right to be indulgent, poetic, and <em>hubristic</em> in prose. i had, at the outset of the draft, recently listened to a reading of Outer Dark (the Cormac novel) by Ed Sala, and i had <em><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><strong>really</strong></span></em> enjoyed it &#8212; so much so that, in order to pay tribute to it <em>and</em> develop a new prosaic style, i decided to emulate cormac's mode of writing, taking his literary principles as i had observed them in Outer Dark and running for as long as i thought necessary. i directly attribute the length of Selenophilia / The Goddess to this.</p> <p>lastly, this piece was <em>so</em> massive to me not just because of the enormous effort that it represented, but because by posting it, i feel i have been able to redeem myself for the thing that started me down writing for the backrooms wiki. during duelcon, i wrote a grand total of <span style="text-decoration: underline;">24,000</span> words for a tale that i felt (and occasionally said) would be the Backrooms Equivalent of ADMONITION. i set out with that goal, writing it like i would a novel; lots of little observations and tangential asides which would hopefully inflate perceived quality, wordcount, and ratings. unfortunately, with that piece, i flew too close to the sun: despite a massive effort from myself, and some general crit from several people on my team, it was outside of my reach &#8212; and by a sizable margin too. by having this up, i feel that i have been able to show that, as a writer, i <em>am</em> improving, little by little.</p> <p>the ultimate goal that i'm working towards, with this series, is a book. i want to write something that will be remembered as good by many people, something that &#8212; even if it doesn't reach the gifted heights that gifted authors can attain &#8212; aspires to do more than entertain. that is my goal both for this wiki and for the SCP wiki (though the SCP wiki project will take yet more time than FOREFRONT, the series i'm pirouetting about).</p> <p>i hope i acheived this with Selenophilia. it's massive and unkempt and &#8212; i cannot stress this enough &#8212; probably features writing that would be laughed out the room if put before an actual copyeditor&#8230; but it's mine. i wrote it with coffee and determination alone, no input from anyone except on a single paragraph to gauge potential reader interest. knowing i was able to finish this <em>bolsters</em> me, it makes investing my time into writing feel worthy.</p> <p>i hope reading it is worthy to you.</p> </div> </div> </div> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17448917</guid>
				<title>Level 409 - &quot;The Lake of Murmur and Reflections&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17448917/level-409-the-lake-of-murmur-and-reflections</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 04:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>LiminalDoctor</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>8559878</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It definitely has the drawbacks of a new author and no crit. There's some issues that would be helped a lot by a few rounds of crit. If you keep at it after the con is over, you'll be able to turn this into something really interesting.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17448267</guid>
				<title>Level 878 - &quot;The Lasting Warmth&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17448267/level-878-the-lasting-warmth</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 17:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Wynths</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9594206</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><strong>NOTE:</strong> Your image is broken on my end; I use a VPN for my Internet, and the source link you use for the first and final photos are hosted off-site. I would fix this myself, but it seems you have to, <span class="printuser avatarhover"><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/klammolt" ><img class="small" src="https://www.wikidot.com/avatar.php?userid=9397782&amp;amp;size=small&amp;amp;timestamp=1763580743" alt="Klammolt" style="background-image:url(https://www.wikidot.com/userkarma.php?u=9397782)" /></a><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/klammolt" >Klammolt</a></span></p> <div class="collapsible-block"> <div class="collapsible-block-folded"><a class="collapsible-block-link" href="javascript:;">+&nbsp;Open&nbsp;Larger&nbsp;Review</a></div> <div class="collapsible-block-unfolded" style="display:none"> <div class="collapsible-block-unfolded-link"><a class="collapsible-block-link" href="javascript:;">-&nbsp;Close</a></div> <div class="collapsible-block-content"> <p><strong>technical execution: I mean this in the most granular and literal sense possible: on a sentence by sentence basis, how many of these would I pick out as good and memorable?</strong></p> <p>i have no comment here; the writing is competently done, and actually pretty alright when it comes to the offset's description of the Aertehl. I will, however, compliment the inclusion of precise meteorological data &#8212; it helps make this feel like an actual file kept by an actual large organization &#8212; even if some of it, like the knowledge of precise wind speeds 5 kilometers in the air, feels like it would realistically be beyond the MEG's ability or will to measure.</p> <p><strong>content: here, i'm referring to the narrative of the page &#8212; do I think it is memorable, consistent and unique? this also plays in with imagery: do I <em>feel</em> the narrative with what you choose to show me?</strong></p> <p>[See Below]</p> </div> </div> </div> <p><strong>SUMMARY:</strong> honestly? this is fine, but it's uninterestingly fine. the worldbuilding here reminds me of my own experience writing my own Folklorecon entry, <a href="https://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/selenophilia" target="_blank">Selenophilia</a>, where I had no real idea of what I wanted to do. except, rather than go for something that would be unique and was layered, I feel like the piece simply leaves the idea of the Aertehl, the Elder, and the Young One be, and doesn't do much with them outside of writing a note and setting up a curious photographic stinger. of course, I don't expect a massive world within the bounds of a thousand words, but I <em>do</em> think that implying a larger and more complex, morally grey history &#8212; instead of just having a prosperous society that is reduced to a single individual <em>off-page</em> &#8212; within the note would have gone a long way towards my enjoyment of the piece.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17448265</guid>
				<title>Entity 85 - &quot;Nymphs&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17448265/entity-85-nymphs</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 17:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>LiminalDoctor</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>8559878</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I like this concept a lot. It's definitely not typical of the Backrooms but it works really well. My biggest issue with this page is in the wording. There's a lot of really beautiful stuff here but sometimes it feels a bit rigid. Could've done with a bit of crit to iron it out. Otherwise tho this is a really solid concept that's well executed. Also I'm a big fan of this being told like a tale. It's easy to take a concept like this and try to make it at least a little clinical but this story telling way of writing the page is perfect!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17448233</guid>
				<title>Object 53 - &quot;Skin of a maighdeann-mhara&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17448233/object-53-skin-of-a-maighdeann-mhara</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>KillerOreo52</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9751782</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Really glad I could crit this ^^</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17448190</guid>
				<title>Entity 299 - &quot;The Kraken&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17448190/entity-299-the-kraken</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 15:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>exotichive</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9462964</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <div class="blockquote" style="text-align: center; font-family: var(--mono-font); font-size: 90%; font-style: italic; padding: 1rem; margin: 1rem;"> <p>Anyways, let's see what else I, uh&#8230; It was Coney Island. They called Coney Island, &quot;the playground of the world.&quot; There was no place like it, in the whole world, like Coney Island when I was a youngster. [&#8230;] Anyways, uh, I&#8230; uh&#8230; you know&#8230; I even got &#8212; when I was, uh, when I was very small, I even got lost at Coney Island, but they found me. On the, on, on the beach. And we used to sleep on the beach here, sleep overnight. They don't do that anymore. Things changed, you see.</p> <p><span style="font-size:110%;"><strong><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cQcE4_7-X78&amp;t=72s">They don't sleep anymore on the beach...</a></strong></span></p> </div> <p style="text-align: center;">this is our entry for <a href="http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/folklorecon2025">folklorecon2025</a>. hope u enjoy.</p> <p style="text-align: center;">n shout out to <span class="printuser avatarhover"><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/praetor3005" ><img class="small" src="https://www.wikidot.com/avatar.php?userid=8321734&amp;amp;size=small&amp;amp;timestamp=1763264700" alt="Praetor3005" style="background-image:url(https://www.wikidot.com/userkarma.php?u=8321734)" /></a><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/praetor3005" >Praetor3005</a></span> n <span class="printuser avatarhover"><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/liminaldoctor" ><img class="small" src="https://www.wikidot.com/avatar.php?userid=8559878&amp;amp;size=small&amp;amp;timestamp=1763264700" alt="LiminalDoctor" style="background-image:url(https://www.wikidot.com/userkarma.php?u=8559878)" /></a><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/liminaldoctor" >LiminalDoctor</a></span> for giving last minute crits for this lol</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17447392</guid>
				<title>Phenomenon 71 - &quot;The Counting Plague&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17447392/phenomenon-71-the-counting-plague</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 03:48:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Br Miller</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9291039</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>1</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17447383</guid>
				<title>POI - Molly</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17447383/poi-molly</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 03:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Br Miller</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9291039</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>A friendly ghost was a nice concept for a Folklore Con entry 👻</p> <p>But you mentioned that you made this in ten minutes? That does show. It has some SPAG issues (Text going off one of the text boxes as an example) and the writing is a bit hard to follow.</p> <p>No voting for now, but I think this page has potential if more time was spent on it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17446894</guid>
				<title>Level 682 - &quot;Suspicion by Suspicion&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17446894/level-682-suspicion-by-suspicion</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 13:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Light_Nate</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9514519</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I read it in the crit state and still like it. I love the chararization of different groups and the text itself.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17444272</guid>
				<title>The Lone Sorcerer</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17444272/the-lone-sorcerer</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 14:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>CharaTheArchivist</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>8330689</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>this could genuinely be a series on here. the writing is absolutely phenomenal, and the note is really well-executed. doing first-person writing can be real tough sometimes (saying this as a fellow first-person writer). the theme is also perfect for this type of thing.<br /> overall, this is well deserving of an upvote :3<br /> (also you should probably change &quot;Sorceror&quot; to &quot;Sorcerer&quot;. you had it write in the heading but not the page title)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17442507</guid>
				<title>Joke Entity PL-2 – &quot;Fly&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17442507/joke-entity-pl-2-fly</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 06:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Light_Nate</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9514519</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Buzz buzzzz buzzz buzzzz buyuuzzz buzzzz buzzz buzzzz buyuuzzz buzzzz buzzz buzzzz buyuuzzzbuzzzz buzzz buzzzz buyuuzzz buzzzz buzzz buzzzz buyuuzzzbuzzzz buzzz buzzzz buyuuzzz buzzzz buzzz buzzzz buyuuzzz</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17442358</guid>
				<title>Jeantober</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17442358/jeantober</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 22:37:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>centurys lute</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>8580783</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>the only thing wrong about the art page category was that none of the pages were about jean meiers</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17442213</guid>
				<title>Entity 151 - &quot;Finnioth&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17442213/entity-151-finnioth</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 17:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Gen_isis</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9580344</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hail Finnioth the epic fish</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17442025</guid>
				<title>Akmē Espionage Agency Theme</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17442025/akme-espionage-agency-theme</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 13:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>XTheLock_</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9716194</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I love this theme.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17441896</guid>
				<title>Unumbered Level - &quot;Level -1 - 1 Second is all it takes ...”</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17441896/unumbered-level-level-1-1-second-is-all-it-takes</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>HN0</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>8616741</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The oldest folklore, the only superpower with countless tales and the one, that writes its own stories, and still&#8230; the one beyond our reach.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17434966</guid>
				<title>Lantern Archive Theme</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17434966/lantern-archive-theme</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>scutoid studios</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>8055329</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Definitely try it yourselves. Until my next theme, ciao</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17432117</guid>
				<title>The Kingdom of Nowhere</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17432117/the-kingdom-of-nowhere</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>centurys lute</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>8580783</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <div style="text-align: center;"> <p><em>The woods are lovely, dark and deep,</em><br /> <em>But I have promises to keep,</em><br /> <em>And miles to go before I sleep,</em><br /> <em>And miles to go before I sleep.</em></p> </div> <hr /> <div class="blockquote" style="font-size: 80%; text-align: center; width: fit-content; margin: 1rem auto;"> <p>　<strong>Thank you to:</strong><br /> <span class="printuser avatarhover"><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/drakimoto" ><img class="small" src="https://www.wikidot.com/avatar.php?userid=5255688&amp;amp;size=small&amp;amp;timestamp=1762217193" alt="DrAkimoto" style="background-image:url(https://www.wikidot.com/userkarma.php?u=5255688)" /></a><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/drakimoto" >DrAkimoto</a></span> <span class="printuser avatarhover"><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/schulzenreich" ><img class="small" src="https://www.wikidot.com/avatar.php?userid=7844614&amp;amp;size=small&amp;amp;timestamp=1762217193" alt="Schulzenreich" style="background-image:url(https://www.wikidot.com/userkarma.php?u=7844614)" /></a><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/schulzenreich" >Schulzenreich</a></span> <span class="printuser avatarhover"><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/scutoid-studios" ><img class="small" src="https://www.wikidot.com/avatar.php?userid=8055329&amp;amp;size=small&amp;amp;timestamp=1762217193" alt="scutoid studios" style="background-image:url(https://www.wikidot.com/userkarma.php?u=8055329)" /></a><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/scutoid-studios" >scutoid studios</a></span><br /> for stopping to look over my silly stream of consciousness.</p> </div> <hr /> <div style="text-align: right;"> <p><sub>&quot;Stopping by Woods on a Snowy Evening&quot; by Robert Frost.</sub></p> </div> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17427785</guid>
				<title>Entity TH-1 - &quot;Handprints&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17427785/entity-th-1-handprints</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 01:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>calf-0</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9454668</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><strong>GOOD translation</strong>. looking forward to more of your works in the future!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17426616</guid>
				<title>Sister Owl</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17426616/sister-owl</link>
				<description>A POI from the Followers of Jerry.</description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Lady Cognitia</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9753692</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><strong>Article link:</strong> <a href="http://backrooms-sandbox-2.wikidot.com/lady-cognitia">http://backrooms-sandbox-2.wikidot.com/lady-cognitia</a></p> <p><strong>Article Name:</strong> Sister Owl</p> <p><strong>Brief Description:</strong> A look at a person of interest belonging to the Followers of Jerry. Calm, humanist and spiritual while holding the embers of piety. Above all else, she witnesses.</p> <p><strong>Critique Focus:</strong> I’m looking a green light for my article, which I think to be finished. If you don’t think so, I’d also love some critique as it’s my first ever wikidot article. I’ve been a long time lurker since mid 2022, and would love to make my first article as good as it can be.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17421261</guid>
				<title>Entity 80 - &quot;Before Eternal Sleep&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17421261/entity-80-before-eternal-sleep</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 21:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Wondrous Expanse</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9388223</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Second ever post and it's for a con! Whaaaaaaattttt.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17416163</guid>
				<title>Level 188 - &quot;Causing&#039;s Button&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17416163/level-188-causing-s-button</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 02:27:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BlueSignet</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>7867242</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>You'll have to forgive me if I seem like I'm rambling. I am currently sick but wanted to explain why I voted the way I did.</p> <p>Overall, I am a bit let down by the page. I think the opening paragraph serves as a fine hook, but as I continued to read, the more and more the page started to feel unpolished and rushed. I believe if I was a casual reader, I would have stopped reading after the first div box. I did read the rest of your page to be thorough and to give places where you could improve.</p> <p>So starting with the first div box:</p> <p>1. It's factually untrue that you can't view past messages on Discord. It's <em>hard</em> sometimes, yes, but not impossible. You can even filter by username and start from the beginning of when they started to post on a server. This was the first thing that took me out of the page, that the research wasn't done.</p> <p>2. Then there is a broken image of a screenshot. It's lazy to say that it can't be shown because it isn't CC compliant. In-universe, the General Public Database is probably not CC. Our wiki is in order to comply with people's intellectual property. There can absolutely be screenshots of fake Discord messages as there pages that do it on our website, and having the fake conversation would have gone a long way to establishing the credibility of the page and build up the suspense of this urban legend.</p> <p>3. We're then told 3-hand about the screenshots, which does nothing to entice me into the page.</p> <p>The reason why this first paragraph fails is because the page fundamentally doesn't understand one of the appeals of the urban legend, especially internet ones. A lot of the draw <em>comes</em> from the research. The main character had to go on a journey, traversing chat rooms, various forums, and old archives to even find proof of something existing. This builds tension within the page, which is what keeps people reading.</p> <p>The next div box is fine actually. It does its job well and there are places where it attempts to use all the senses, not just sight and sound. I think it could be expanded on just a touch more, but overall, if combined with the revised version of the first div, could work.</p> <p>The last div I think is the most disappointing. I did like the idea of the buttons and the silliness contrasted with the serious. However, the description of the level itself is only the bare minimum and doesn't use purposeful language to not only describe what the level looks like, but to also get me to feel the vibes. Also, this is the place where we get to experiment with the buttons and only three things happened, which is&#8230; disappointing if these buttons can do almost anything. Also this part:</p> <blockquote> <p>But the most terrible thing was yet to come: my right thumb was suddenly and cleanly cut off. How scary that was!</p> </blockquote> <p>is not very scary. It's not scary because the narrator is detached from the whole situation, which means I can't be scared if they aren't. &quot;How scary that was&quot; tells me it's scary, but it doesn't feel scary. This what we mean by &quot;show don't tell.&quot; Show me that this is scary through the emotions and actions of the narrator. Are they sweating? How is their heart rate? Don't have them tell me it's scary and expect me to believe it.</p> <p>Also, I don't believe the offset of how the level is written is doing the page any favors. It is &quot;a place that is weird&quot; and nothing more than that. I suggest cutting it completely if this page is rewritten.</p> <p>There is potential in the page if you wanted to rewrite it, but I heavily suggest getting multiple rounds of critique and heavily adjusting the page. Also, do check out our guides, as they're meant to help new writers succeed on our wiki.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17408978</guid>
				<title>Abdallah Amr</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17408978/abdallah-amr</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 12:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>ReyDay</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>8781221</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>based author page</p> <p>- your loving husband</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17403373</guid>
				<title>Hi</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17403373/hi</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 01:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Poocubed_princess99</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9939908</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hi, I like math and science. I am an 2 year experienced in mathematics and great at games like GD,MC,CRK and chess. That's for now.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17402601</guid>
				<title>Ancient House</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17402601/ancient-house</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 20:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Praetor3005</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>8321734</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The page was pretty enjoyable! I think you managed to translate the piece well, and I felt really immersed in the setting. That being said, there are still some weird translation choices, like the genderless skeleton being referred to with male pronouns, or some weird jumps between past and present tense. I can't judge due to not being able to read the original, so I'll still upvote because at the end of the day, I think you did a pretty good job! Looking forward to more RU translations.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17402030</guid>
				<title>How do you make text fade?</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17402030/how-do-you-make-text-fade</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 17:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Hxky</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9506767</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>If someone could give me the syntax code to make text seem like it is fading, or a page that has text like this, that would be wonderful.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17393425</guid>
				<title>Everything disappears when you close your eyes</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17393425/everything-disappears-when-you-close-your-eyes</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 12:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Br Miller</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9291039</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>This article I feel really on the fence about. The first part the article made it seem like the story was exploring the topic of solipsism, but then it suddenly shifts to the protagonist being in denial of the death of their loved one and them desperately trying to take advantage the level's environment to bring them back. The start and end of the article don't seem to have the same theme.</p> <p>This article has some interesting ideas, but I don't know if I like it or not.</p> <p>The CSS was cool though.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17393379</guid>
				<title>The death of innocence</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17393379/the-death-of-innocence</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 12:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Light_Nate</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9514519</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <h1><span>+1</span></h1> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17393312</guid>
				<title>Phenomenon 46 - &quot;The Eye of the Beast&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17393312/phenomenon-46-the-eye-of-the-beast</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 12:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>InspectingCritters</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9419279</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hi. I don't usually make these, but this time I felt like it'd be weird if I didn't. Some may recognize this as my alt draft from Duelcon2025.</p> <p>This is a page about a lot of things. I wrote it with a lot of things running through my mind, in a very dark place. It's about hatred and pain and sleepless nights, about every part of life that pulls at my heart and consumes my skull, about things I can't express more comprehensibly than this very page. It is the rawest thing I have ever written. I have probably called past drafts/pages experimental before, but this one takes the cake. There are a plethora of ways to interpret the meaning here, and all of them are as right as you want them to be.</p> <p>There are a lot of reasons not to like this page, and I figure it might not survive. I'm not sure I really care. I still wrote it regardless.</p> <p>Side trivia: The writing style is heavily inspired by a very specific page. It's probably obvious if you've read it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17378031</guid>
				<title>Suprematism Theme</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17378031/suprematism-theme</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>LemonCat233</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>8651520</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Wish you will like our theme!!</p> <p>Thank you <span class="printuser avatarhover"><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/cakelord114514" ><img class="small" src="https://www.wikidot.com/avatar.php?userid=8507623&amp;amp;size=small&amp;amp;timestamp=1761152310" alt="cakelord114514" style="background-image:url(https://www.wikidot.com/userkarma.php?u=8507623)" /></a><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/cakelord114514" >cakelord114514</a></span> for the TechLight!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17370738</guid>
				<title>Walls</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17370738/walls</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 21:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>KkKkK_1234</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>8075479</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Finally, I saw the first Russian-English translation. I hope more Russian articles will be translated into English in the future.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17354542</guid>
				<title>Level 311 - &quot;The Yellowrooms&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17354542/level-311-the-yellowrooms</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BlueSkiesAbove</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9049486</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>This page is a metanarrative test of morality. It's also a sequel to <a href="http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/phenomenon-23">Phenomenon 23</a>, in a way.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17340287</guid>
				<title>The Splice of Life</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17340287/the-splice-of-life</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 20:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Gen_isis</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9580344</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Great addition to the first story.</p> <p>I could just be dumb but I wasn’t sure where this story took place but I assume that’s the point lol</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17338867</guid>
				<title>Level 75 - &quot;Liminality&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17338867/level-75-liminality</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 12:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Gen_isis</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9580344</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>…but wow I love this. I love this a lot. It’s a very wholesome view on backrooms through all the turmoil.</p> <p>+1. This is nice.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17338770</guid>
				<title>Level 75 - &quot;Liminality&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17338770/level-75-liminality</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 11:52:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Br Miller</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9291039</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Something is oddly familiar about this place.</p> <p>A complex of decrepit blue and white rooms with the floor covered by a thick layer of yellow sand, accompanied by the perpetual sound of rain.</p> <p>You've been here before, haven't you?</p> The Sandrooms is one of the most visited levels in Backrooms, yet almost no one knows it exists. However, this changed following the post of a viral 'Liminal Playlist' video on BackTube.<br /> <img src="https://backrooms-wiki.wdfiles.com/local--files/level-75/Sandrooms%20Photo%201.jpg" alt="Sandrooms%20Photo%201.jpg" class="image" /><br /> <img src="https://backrooms-wiki.wdfiles.com/local--files/level-75/Playlist%20For%20Exploring%20Liminality.png" alt="Playlist%20For%20Exploring%20Liminality.png" class="image" />
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17326822</guid>
				<title>Level 425 -  Blink Outside The Box</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17326822/level-425-blink-outside-the-box</link>
				<description>*sung to the tune of Without Me by Eminem*
Guess who’s back
And is dead
From writing
This level
nananana</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:37:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Gen_isis</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9580344</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>*sigh* I took too long and my desired level number was taken so here we are making a new thread</p> <p><a href="http://backrooms-sandbox-2.wikidot.com/gen-isis-3">http://backrooms-sandbox-2.wikidot.com/gen-isis-3</a></p> <p>I’m still in need of a couple more critiques, any feedback would be greatly appreciated!</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17304017</guid>
				<title>Level 595 - &quot;The Damned Dam&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17304017/level-595-the-damned-dam</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 15:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Wondrous Expanse</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9388223</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>They dammed the dam and now it's damned.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17301716</guid>
				<title>Essay</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17301716/essay</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 07:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>KillerOreo52</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9751782</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Yes. Very essay.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17285150</guid>
				<title>Level 108 - &quot;Fertile Grounds&quot;</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17285150/level-108-fertile-grounds</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 21:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Hxky</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>9506767</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Interesting history, I really like the journal section.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17285063</guid>
				<title>DON&#039;T YOU WANT TO GO FUCKING APESHIT</title>
				<link>http://backrooms-wiki.wikidot.com/forum/t-17285063/don-t-you-want-to-go-fucking-apeshit</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 21:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>BlueSignet</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>7867242</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I've had this written for awhile, but just haven't published it aha.</p> <p>Thanks <span class="printuser avatarhover"><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/praetor3005" ><img class="small" src="https://www.wikidot.com/avatar.php?userid=8321734&amp;amp;size=small&amp;amp;timestamp=1759440384" alt="Praetor3005" style="background-image:url(https://www.wikidot.com/userkarma.php?u=8321734)" /></a><a href="http://www.wikidot.com/user:info/praetor3005" >Praetor3005</a></span> for encouraging me that this would be a good coldpost. If it fails, I'm gonna get you :3</p> <p>Anyway, I love the Speednoclippers. They're just adrenaline junkies. Little goobers. I like to think that the American ones are even more thrill-seekers than their Chinese counterparts. They need more love here.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>